

## Mihir Trivedi

## R&D Engineer

portfolio - https://mihir9795.github.io/

+91 7405388567

mihir9795agmail.com

## ABOUT

Focused and enthusiastic developer with a keen interest in software development and artificial intelligence. By comprehensive exposure to the underlying concepts and applying them vividly to various projects, my love for these domains came into being. I am a passionate individual who thrives to build and apply algorithms to solve real-world industry problems.

tor CUV
Worked

Engineer R&D \_\_\_\_\_\_ 2019-Present

Kalyani strategic management services - Pune, IN

Working as a Project Lead with a team of 3+ members

Working on FFT, ML ,AI algorithms to predict live machine health and predict any failures and remaining useful life of machine

Worked on Pufferfish - open source Ventilator software and hardware development OVID-19 patients.

in Project Sanjeevani , a pulse dose delivery system for COVID-19 Patients

## **PROFESSIONAL** EXPERIENCE

\_\_\_\_\_ 2018-2019 Mechatronics Engineer

Aliyance Mechatronics - Ahmedabad, IN

Worked for India's 1st Roboseum - a project awarded to Govt. of Gujrat, India. Worked as Technical head for electronics team for roboseum project. Worked on prototyping and developing different robots for the robseum including AMY-waiter robot, Robo Soccer, Painter robot, Badminton Robot, Robo Kitchen, Robo Cafe, Technical Documentation of roboseum for GCSC officials.

Automation Engineer

2017-2017

Rasik Industries - Ahmedabad, IN

Worked on automation of special purpose machines such as automatic surface grinder and automatic stamp machine to stamp products.

**EDUCATION** 

Ganpat University

2014 - 2017

Mehsana, IN

B. Tech Mechatronics

Gujarat Technological University 2009-2013

Mehsana, IN

Diploma Mechatronics